[{"answer": "You said you weren't a hundred percent on this. You said that like a week ago. Can I come up there", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Really? You feel happier...  Please don't tell my friend anything please, until we've talked more", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No. I don't want to see you", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I need to tell him. And we need to tell my friend. Did he do his homework", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Be careful the way you pull on that child's arm. You'll take it out of its socket", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't care how you treat your child as long as you don't hurt him", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "People always pee in the pool", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'll bet you 500 dollars there's pee in that pool", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I don't know if my friend is gay", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Your mom is pregnant", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He might be, it's very common", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No she isn't", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's the Forum", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "She was in a cult", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I guess I said something", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He wants to know. If I don't tell him, he figures it out", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You're making me do the whole fucking thing", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He brought up", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I can tell you're lying", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't trust her", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "We didn't, mom", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "She really loves you. She does", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, you're not. You're not", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, you haven't kept your mouth shut! No you haven't...kept your mouth shut..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What does that mean", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I mean, what can we do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I was thinking", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Will you do it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You don't like my friend because you're not attracted to him", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. I won't do that for you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I...I need some clothes and things", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Okay. I'll tell him to get the hell out of our house", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's not too sweet? They sometimes make their stuff too sweet", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I miss you too. Maybe we should do another seminar", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Did you do something", "docId": "Margot-at-the-Wedding.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I mean, why is the wedding not happening? Is there something that you did", "qsentId": 36}]